export const Questions = [
    {
        prompt: "Q1: What is the capital city of Canada ?",
        optionA: "Toronto",
        optionB: "Vancouver",
        optionC: "Ottawa" ,
        optionD: "Edmonton",
        answer: "C",
    },

    {
        prompt: "Q2: What is the largest country on earth ?",
        optionA: "Brazil",
        optionB: "China",
        optionC: "Russia",
        optionD: "USA",
        answer: "C",
      },
      {
        prompt: "Q3: Mount Kilimanjaro is found in ... ? ",
        optionA: "Tunisia",
        optionB: "South Africa",
        optionC: "Egypt",
        optionD: "Tanzania",
        answer: "D",
      },

      {
        prompt: "Q4: Which country has a tree on its flag ? ",
        optionA: "Lebanon",
        optionB: "Argentina",
        optionC: "Mongolia",
        optionD: "New Zealand",
        answer: "A",
      },

      {
        prompt: "Q5: What is the longest river on earth ? ",
        optionA: "Amazon",
        optionB: "Yangtze",
        optionC: "Mississippi",
        optionD: "Nile",
        answer: "D",
      },

      {
        prompt: "Q6: What is the capital of Florida ? ",
        optionA: "Miami",
        optionB: "Tallahassee",
        optionC: "Orlando",
        optionD: "Tampa Bay",
        answer: "B",
      },

      {
        prompt: "Q7: What is the most populated country ? ",
        optionA: "China",
        optionB: "India",
        optionC: "USA",
        optionD: "Indonesia",
        answer: "A",
      },

      {
        prompt: "Q8: Where can you find the Colosseum ? ",
        optionA: "Paris",
        optionB: "Venice",
        optionC: "Berlin",
        optionD: "Rome",
        answer: "D",
      },

      {
        prompt: "Q9: Which continent has the Andes Mountains ? ",
        optionA: "North America",
        optionB: "South America",
        optionC: "Asia",
        optionD: "Africa",
        answer: "B",
      },

      {
        prompt: "Q10: What is the capital city of Australia ? ",
        optionA: "Sydney",
        optionB: "Melbourne",
        optionC: "Canberra",
        optionD: "Perth",
        answer: "C",
      },



];